Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg
1926-1997
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Ginsberg, Allen
MSS.PHOTO.0450
26 Linear Feet 88,000 images
Photographs of and by poet Allen Ginsberg and colleagues.
Other Finding Aids
Guide to the Allen Ginsberg Papers, 1937-1994 (M0733)
Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983-1996 (Mss Media 0004)
Arrangement
This collection of roughly 88,000 photographs has been arranged into three principal series. Series 1 contains photographic prints and is further divided into the subseries: Ginsberg by Others (subseries 1.1), Photographs by Others (Subseries 1.2), Photographs of Friends (1.3) and Ginsberg Family Photographs (1.4). Series 2. Contact Sheets includes numbered contact prints which have been described the print level. Series 3. contains numbered negatives sheets.
Scope and Content of Collection
Contains photographic prints, contact sheets and negatives of Ginsberg and his associates.
Biography / Administrative History
Irwin Allen Ginsberg was born on June 3, 1926 in Newark, New Jersey to Louis and Naomi (Levy) Ginsberg. American poet, author, lecturer, and teacher who was one of the core members of the Beat Generation of American author's in the 1950's and early 1960's along with Jack Kerouac, William S. Burroughs, and Neal Cassady. He died of complications of liver cancer on April 6, 1997.
Acquisition Information
Accessions 2001-073, 2002-109, 2002-238, 2005-113.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Photoprints.; American literature -- 20th century.; Ginsberg, Allen
- Series 1: Photographic Prints, Series 1; 26 manuscript boxes (13 linear ft.)
  - Ginsberg by Others, Subseries 1.1; 20 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box (10.25 linear ft.)
    Scope and Contents note
    Subseries 1.1 Ginsberg by Others is arranged chronologically and contains photographic prints of Ginsberg from 1926 thru 1997.
    - Ginsberg 1930's: Pictures of Allen, 1926 - 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Ginsberg, Naomi
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1940 - 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1945 - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Includes images of his Maritime Service and images from his time at Columbia University
      Columbia University
    - Allen Ginsberg: Self Portrait, 1945 - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1950 - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Michael Sand
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1955 - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Anslinger, Harry J.; Orlovsky, Peter; john Cohen; Whalen, Philip; Price Daniel; Mike McClure
    - Allen Ginsberg (Also See: Mexico - 1955 [Pics Not By Allen]), 1955 - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Includes image of Montgomery St. room, San Francisco where 'Howl' was composed and images from Allen Ginsberg's time in Paris
      Montgomery Street, San Francisco; Paris; Dennis Cunningham; Amiri Baraka; Newman, Albert; Muriel Kallis Newman; Orlovsky, Peter; Harold Chapman;; Rosenthal, Irving, 1930-; Corso, Gregory; Ed Freeman
    - Harry Redl Photos (Have Negs and Copy Negs), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Includes images from San Francsico and images from Afternoon of Berkeley Poetry Reading, "Moloch"
      San Francisco; Berkeley
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1960 - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Images from Young Lamas Home School in New Delhi and images from Tarapith, Calcutta, Benares, Athens,
      Tarapith; New Delhi; Athens (Greece); Calcutta; Benares; Shakti Chaterjee;; Sargent Johnson; Sally Stanford; Richard Harrity; Orlovsky, Peter; Young Lamas Home School; Wing; Varda; Ashor; Bill Ryan; Ellie Dorfman; Evan S. Conwell; Florence Allen; Leary, Timothy; Henri Lenoir; Lincoln Clarkes; Nagendia Nath Sankar; Whalen, Philip
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Images from Paradise Alley,
      Leroi McLucas;; Thelonious Monk
    - Allen Ginsberg (photos by others), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Images from Athens, Tangiers
      Tangiers; Athens (Greece); Larry Helenberg; Larry Warlich; Leroi Jones;; Corso, Gregory; Orlovsky, Peter
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Images from Calcutta, New Dehli
      Calcutta; New Delhi; Joanna Kyger; Snyder, Gary; Orlovsky, Peter
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Images of City Lights Bookstore, San Francisco
      San Francisco (Calif.); Anne Buchannan; Bob Brannaman; Allen Russo; Beach; C. Plymell; Bob Kaufman; City Lights Bookstore; Charles Plymell; Ellen Tallman; Leary; Warren Tallman; Gary Goodrow; Whalen, Philip; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence
    - Photos of Allen Ginsberg, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Frank O'Hara; Camille McGrath
    - 405-6 Cuba, Prague, Moscow, 1965; Slides and Phtotgraphic Images (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Images of Auschwitz, Havana, Berkeley, London, City Lights Bookstore in San Francisco, Albert Hall in London reading "The Change," King of May Parade, Newcastle, and spy photo taken from file of Prague secret police
      Berkeley (Calif.) -- History.; Auschwitz (Concentration camp); San Francisco (Calif.); Prague; Newcastle; London; Havana (Cuba); Albert Hall; Bill Craddock; Pavel Beren; Patti A. Warner; Nicamor Parra; Miguel Grinberg; Michael McClure; Larry Keenan Jr.; Karou Sekine; City Lights Bookstore; Cabea; Bruce Conners; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Bixby
    - 405-6 Cuba, Prague, Moscow, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Images from trip to Prague and Albert Hall
      Prague; Tom Zabora; Zdena Salivarova; Josef Skorecky; Sue Miles; Albert Hall; Jarmilia Emmerova
    - Washington Square - ?, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Images from a Washington Square Park Reading against Park Department Wishes Legal Test
      Washington Square Park; Kaoru Sekine
    - England, Albert Hall, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Images from Albert Hall, Prague, Moscow
      Moscow; Prague; Trocchi, Alexander; Yevteshenko; Corso, Gregory; Albert Hall; Rodevtsensky; Ginsberg, Allen; Basil Bunting; Tom Pickard; Mangala Mitra; Pavel Beran; Aksivnov; Lanon
    - Pictures of Allen Ginsberg, Warsaw, Poland, 1965 and 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Wojciech Antoni Iwanczak
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Images from Czechoslovakia and Cuba
      Czechoslovakia; L. Ryat Neogy; Ernst Jandle; Corso, Gregory; Tom Marcher; Ted Hughes; A. Vognesensky; Alexander Nagy; William McClure; Aleksander M. Haupt; Tony B. Coe; Anselm Hollo
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Images from Prague and the Berkeley Poetry Conference
      Berkeley (Calif.) -- History.; Prague; Alexander Nagy; Stephen Eric Shore; Berkeley Poetry Conference; Tom Moeschler; Jim Shimla; Tove Neville; Jon Gilbert Fox; Kaoru Sekine; Les A. Goldsmith; Mariano Ferre; Museo Hemingway
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Images from London, Cuba
      London; Cuba; Barbara Rubin; Larry Keenan Jr.; Jon Gilbert Fox; Corso, Gregory; Michael McClure; Paul Krassner; Dale Smith; Paul Schumach; Dale D. Smith
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Images from Berkeley Poetry Conference
      Tove Neville; Miss Moore;; Berkeley Poetry Conference
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Images of Pisa; Boston University
      Pisa; Boston University; Heari, Adrian; Steven Leech; Richard Baker;; Marc Olmstead; D. Cirpriani
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Images of San Francisco Human Be-In; Johns Hopkins, Baltimore Institute; Portofino, Italy; Image of Allen at Passaic Falls
      Portofino, Italy; Passaic Falls; San Francisco (Calif.); James W. Smith; Pound, Ezra; Johns Hopkins, Baltimore Institute; Tom Law; Fernanda Pivano; Stanley T.; Paul Kagan; Ron Zimardi; Lisa Bachelis;; Lisa Law
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Image of peace march
      Carey Winfrey
    - Rueters UPI Photographs, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      UPI Roto Service Story and Photographs. "A Poet In Our Time" Story and Photos by Gerald Davis, United Press International.
      Gerald Davis
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 - 1967; Slides and Photographic Images (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Miko-Cha Masa; Nelson F. Marek; Lloyd Ziff; Mike Aldrich; E. Soltsass Jr.; Paul Sequeira; Dizzy Gillespie; Suwa-no-se
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Images of Human Be-In; Passaic Falls; Pisa; Senate Judiciary Subcommittee Hearings on LSD and Marijuana at the 89th Congress
      Passaic Falls; Pisa; San Francisco (Calif.); Patti Smith; Ginsberg, Louis; Maretta Greer; Snyder, Gary; Robert Mapplethorpe; Jerry Benjamin; Paul Kagan; Tamiya Naoi; Joe Zimel; Senate Judiciary Subcommittee; Jerry Schmidt; Louis and Edith
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 -1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Images of Be-In at Golden Gate Park; Venice, Italy
      Golden Gate Park (San Francisco, Calif.); Venice (Italy); William Kinter; Paul Sequeira; D. P. Cipriani; E. Setisass Jr.; James W. Smith; Holub, Leo; Jim Coke; Paul Kagan
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1966 -1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Images of Ginsberg at demonstrations in Washington, D.C.
      Washington, D.C.; James W. Smith; Scott Hess
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Pictures from Florida, Chicago, Tuscon, Cherry Valley
      Chicago, Ill.; Florida; Tuscon; Cherry Valley; John Wood; Maureen Magee; Larry Johnson; Paul Lubenkov; Leon Stokesbury; Paul P. Kies; Mable Johnson; Whalen, Philip; Rick Ryan; Bob Ross; Scott Hyde; Spencer Smith; Stanford, Frank; Swami Bha?; Jim Whitehead
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Pictures from New York City's Gotham Book Mart and Gallery; Circumambulation of Mt. Tamalpais Collier Spring Buddha's Birthday Anniversary; NASA Houston; Democratic National Convention Chicago 1968; Cherry Valley
      Cherry Valley; New York City; Mount Tamalpais; Collier Spring; Chicago, Ill.; Houston; Whalen, Philip; Swami B (?); Tony; Will Quong; Michael Cooper; Perry Richardson; Andreas Brown; Andrew Hoyim; Orlovsky, Peter; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration; Gotham Book Mart; Daniel Dole; Clement Hurd; Bill Berkson; Steloff, Frances; Democratic Party (U.S.).; Bill Kwong; Genet, Jean; Bobbie Louise Creeley; Bob Greensfelder; Karou Sekine; John Giorno (?); Matthew Davis; Marella Geery; Burroughs, William S.; Hoffman, Abbie; Joel Oppenheimer
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Naomi Savage; Don Eddy; Fred Haberer
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Images from Gotham Book Mart and Gallery in New York City; Circumambulation of Mount Tamalpais Buddha's Birthday Anniversary Collier Spring'; Forum on Permissive Society
      Mount Tamalpais; Collier Spring; New York City; Don Eddy; Fred Haberer; Bob Greenfelder; Gotham Book Mart; Charters, Ann; Norman Cousins
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Naomi Savage
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Images from Hospital, Chicago Convention,
      Chicago, Ill.; Kerstin Fraser
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Images from St. Mark's Church Reading, Chicago's Grant Park, Allen Ginsberg recording his first album of Blake songs in NYC, Miami Convention 1968
      Miami, Florida; New York City; Grant Park, Chicago; Boyd, Robert S.; Ray Fisher; Peter Simmondes; Kerstin Fraser; Harold Strauss, Rajat Neogy; Ron Zimardi; St. Mark's Church
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Images from Circumambulation of Mt. Tamalpais Buddha's Birthday Anniversary; Redwood Creek, Muir Woods; and East Peak
      Redwood Creek, Muir Woods; Mount Tamalpais; East Peak; Malanga, Gerard; George Becker; Gary H. Schroeder; Paul Levin; Jim Coke; Irv Steinfink
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1970 - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Images from Times Square, Boston, KQED-FM Studio San Francisco
      San Francisco (Calif.); Boston (Mass.); Times Square, New York City; Roger Miller; Mark PoKemper; KQED-FM; Chris Williams; Andrei Vosnesensky; Ball, Gordon
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1970 - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Images from Calcutta; Art Festival Cherry Valley; Angels of Light; Karma Patrol; Psychedelic Venus Church; Committee on Poetry; Warsaw Walowa Poland; San Francisco Peace Day; Miami, Florida
      San Francisco (Calif.); Warsaw, Poland; Cherry Valley; Calcutta; Miami, Florida; Arthur Furst; Committee on Poetry; Dale Warner; Charters, Ann; Gary H. Schroeder; Jay Stoane; Jonas Kover; Jozef Balcerak; Yevtushenko, Yevgeny Aleksandrovich; Karma Patrol; Michal Wojcikiewicz; Nirmala; Psychedelic Venus Church; Richard Avedon; Angels of Light; Roger Miller; Art Usherson
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1970 - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Images from Angels of Light Concert at the Free Cabaret, Karma Patrol, India
      India; D.P. Cipriani; Bill Yoscary; Mark Green; Jerry Walker; Roger Miller
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1970 - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Images from John Sandier (?) Freedom Rally, Ann Arbor, Michigan; Washington D.C.; New Orleans; San Francisco Peace Rally; Visa/Passport Photos; doing Blake II album at Pacific High Studio; Gotham Book Mart and Gallery party for Snyder, in New York City; India
      San Francisco (Calif.); New York City; India; New Orleans; Washington, D.C.; Ann Arbor, Michigan; Jon Bonny; Ashbery; Jack Miller; Bill Yoscary; Miles; Ball, Gordon; Allen DeLock; Sidney Smith; David Dion deGrazia; Ray Bremser; Denise Feliu; William Bamberger; Bonnie Bremser; Snyder G (?); Charlie Plymel; Gotham Book Mart; Elizabeth Eve deGrazia; Frances Steeoff; Don Allen; Ed deGrazia; Ginsberg, Louis; Steloff, Frances; Gary Gety
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1970 - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Images from Cherry Valley Poetry Forum; Gotham Book Mart and Gallery in New York City; Virginia Commonwealth University; Karma Patrol
      Virginia; Cherry Valley; New York City; Steloff, Frances; Vosnezeusky (?); Andreas Brown; Bill Yoscary; Allan Koss; Ann Waldman; Jan Herman; Ginsberg, Allen; Malanga, Gerard; Orlovsky, Peter; Gianfranco Mantegna; Nancy Fisher; Nanao Sahalic (?); De Loach, Allen; Karma Patrol; John Tetsworth (?); Corso, Gregory; Virginia Commonwealth University; Gotham Book Mart; Uday Shankar; Tarapada Ray
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Images from New York City Central Park; at San Francisco State; Tim Leary Benefit Reading at Everett Junior High School, San Francisco; mixing Allen's tape with Dylan at the Record Planet in New York; Cherry Valley Festival; Be-in; naked men in snow
      Cherry Valley; San Francisco (Calif.); New York; Central Park, New York City; Darleen and Lloyd; Ginsberg, Louis; Orlovsky, Peter; Hugh Rouney ("Wavy Gravy"); Jhardene Necta; Ron Padgett; Ann Waldman; Ball, Gordon; Carl Solomon; Record Planet; Shig and Harold Norse; Carol Gallup; Beck, Julian; San Francisco State University; Dan Ellison; Nanos Valoritis; Miles; Phil Oakes; De Loach, Allen; Judith Molina; Joanna Leary
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Images from and end of war rally in Central Park, New York City; Tim Leary Benefit Reading at Everett Junior High School, San Francisco; El Paso, Texas; Rotterdam and Delft in Holland, Scotland, Sussex, Hofstra
      San Francisco (Calif.); Hofstra; Central Park, New York City; Sussex; Scotland; Rotterdam, Holland; Delft, Holland; El Paso, Texas; Judith Molina; John Beedon; Joan Schroeder; J. Giorno; Beck, Julian; Whalen, Philip; Everett Junior High School; Dr. Horwich; Pelieu, Claude; Ron Atkinson; Wavey Gravey; Snyder, Gary; Orlovsky, Peter; Mary Bunch (?); Ginsberg, Louis
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Images from Rutgers, Newark, The State University of New Jersey; photos of trees Cherry Valley; Hofstra; sit-in arrests at the Miami Republican Convention; Kansas
      Newark, New Jersey; Miami, Florida; Kansas; Cherry Valley; Hofstra; Ball, Gordon; Joan Schroeder; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Jonas Kover; Gary Johnson; D.C. Goings; Whalen, Philip; David Rowe Green?; Alice Beberman; State University of New Jersey; Republican party; Ray Bremser; Mike Geier; Abbott, Berenice.; Larry Sloman
    - Ram Dass, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Orlovsky, Peter; Ram Dass
    - Teton Trip (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Ron Zimardi
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Images from Madison, Wisconsin; Wedding of Generations in Miami; Don Cherry concert in New York City
      New York City; Madison, Wisconsin; Miami, Florida; Orlovsky, Peter; Felieu; Giorno, John.; Barbara Gibson; Denise
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 -1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Images from New York City, Loeb Center, Kansas
      New York City; Kansas; Don Che?; Bob Mann?; Israel Martell?; Pogue, Alan; Ginsberg, Louis; Loeb Center; Layle Silbert; Ball, Gordon; Mike Geier; Bill Randvier?
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 -1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Images from the Turret Bookstore in London; Shaw Theater in London; Kaddish Backstage; Lael House Reconstruction in Black Hawk, Colorado; Orcutt, California; Cherry Valley; Pittsburg, Kansas; Poetry Reading in Boulder; Miami Democratic Convention; political demonstrations at the Miami Republican Convention
      Orcutt, California; Miami, Florida; Boulder; Pittsburg, Kansas; Black Hawk, Colorado; Cherry Valley; London; Ed White; Denis; Jeff Nightbad?; Eugene, Marlyn, Chris; Elsa Dorfman; Shig Murao; Shaw Theater; T.R. Leyde; Steven Smith; Turret; Chez Lois Hennessey Snyder; Turret Bookstore; Carl Solomon; Arthur Furst; Patricia Gozemba; Democratic Party (U.S.).; Chez Lois Hennessey Snyder; Republican party; Robert Bly; Roger Whitaker; Roger Whitticker; Sam Silver; Orlovsky, Peter; Sam Silvey; Jerry Rubin; Jerry Walker; Lael House; Snyder, Gary; Larry Sloman; Mac Anonymouse; Mike Geier; Nanao; Nico Kormer
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1972 -1973; Photographs: Prints + Photographs: Slides + Photographs: `Negatives (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Images from Miami Democratic Convention; Angels of Light, Psychedelic Venus Church; London; Passport photos
      Miami, Florida; New York City; London; Hugh McD?; Sanders, Ed; Jane Bown; Democratic Party (U.S.).; Orlovsky, Peter; Harold Strauss; Larry Sloman; Lubowski; John Gromo; John Wieners; Snyder, Gary; Psychedelic Venus Church; Bill Bukson; Bob McNeely; Oswald Mtshahi?; Angels of Light; M. Boats; Elsa Dorfman; Sam Silver; Diana Henry
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1974 - 1975; Photographs: Prints + Photographs: Negatives (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Images from Naropa University, Boulder, Colorado; Walt Whitman Day at Rutgers, Camden State University of New Jersey; Montreal; signing of book The Fall of America at Rhode Island College; City Lights Bookstore San Francisco; Sacred Heart High School in Boulder; Loeb Center in New York City; Fargo, North Dakota; Gotham Book Mart and Gallery in New York City; Buenos Aires; Columbia University; building a house in Bedrock, California
      New York City; Montreal; New Jersey; Boulder, Colorado; Bedrock, California; San Francisco (Calif.); Buenos Aires; Fargo, North Dakota; Sacred Heart High School; Sarogan Humphrey; Rhode Island College; Corso, Gregory; Rutgers, Camden State University of New Jersey; Shig; Anne Waldman; Tanie McClure; Bill Paul; Sarogan; Bill Yoscary; Whalen, Philip; Shig Murao; Brad Gordon; Mosher, Pamela; Paul Chamberland; Gotham Book Mart; Montgomery; Naropa University; Rhasha A?; Peter Barry Chowka; Jim Humphrey; Orlovsky, Peter; Mark Moodink?; Burroughs, William S.; Loeb Center; Jorge Luis Borges; Joanne McClure; Snyder, Gary; City Lights Bookstore; Carson Schwartz; Trumgpa Rimpoche; Bradford Lyttle; Esteban Moore; David Rome; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Columbia University
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1974 - 1975; Photographs: Prints + Photographs: Slides (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Images from Rhode Island College in Providence; North Dakota; pocket album of photographs from Bedrock, California with Allen and other men at unfinished house; a reading at Columbia University; Rocky Mountain Dharma Center; Sacred Heart High School in Boulder; Gotham Book Mart and Gallery in New York City; letter from Tashi Shimada; reading in Berkeley, California
      North Dakota; Bedrock, California; Boulder, Colorado; New York City; Providence, Rhode Island; Berkeley (Calif.); Rocky Mountain Dharma Center; Sacred Heart High School; Tashi Shimada; Tashi; Leo Vroman; Marc PoKempner; Gotham Book Mart; Mike McClure; Nanao Sahaki?; Paul Levin; Peter Barry Chowka; Rhode Island College; George Nickerson; Lewis, Harry; Gregory Pickup; Jim Humphrey; Jay Bolstin; Kazunobu Yanagi; John Little; Bill Yoscary; Bill Small; Bob Dempleowski; Bob Del Tredici; Columbia University; Ginsberg, Louis; Bradford Lyttle; Snyder, Gary; Denise
    - Rachel Homer collection. Naropa, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Images from Naropa
      Naropa, Colorado; David Rome (?); Whalen, Philip; Orlovsky, Peter; Anne Waldman; Renroche; Chogyam Trungpa Rinpoche; Berrigan, Ted; Sanders, Ed; Rich Fields; Kyger, Joanne.; Peter Worshall; Rachel Homer; Michael Brownstein; Lewes (?); MAc Adams; Karme Thimly Lama (?); Kyger; Jackson Mac Low (?); Dick GallupJoan Agger
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Images from Rose Savage's House; wedding picture of Arthur and Kit Knight and Allen's apartment in Boulder, Colorado; pictures in Salt Lake City, Utah and Fairlawn, New Jersey; Apollinaire's Grave in Paris; reading at Hard Rain Concert; Boston University student union basement lockers where three pounds of grass were confiscated; Naropa University, Boulder, Colorado
      Boulder, Colorado; Fritz Arnold; Eric Morey; Caron Schwartz; Rose Savage; Boston University; Peggy Brademan?; Corso, Gregory; Arthur and Kit Knight; Patricia Maker?; Naropa University; Ino? Robbins
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1976; Photographs: Prints + Photographs: Negatives (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Images from Horseback Riding at Sombrero Ranch in Colorado; Gotham Book Mart and Gallery in New York City
      Colorado; New York City; Denise Mercedes; Gotham Book Mart; Edwin Denby?; Fr. Stelloff; Sombrero Ranch; Anne Waldman; Patti Smith; Bill Yoscary
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Images from Reading at the Corcoran Gallery of Art in Washington D.C.; in Paris, France; St. Cloud, Minnesota; Oktoberfest in Munich; Oakton Community College, Chicago, Illinois; Troubador, Los Angeles; Central Park near Bird Sanctuary Pond; at Varsity Townhouses
      Washington, D.C.; Los Angeles (Calif.); Chicago, Ill.; St. Cloud, Minnesota; Munich; Paris (France); Central Park; Ball, Gordon; Burroughs, William S.; Brian Gysiu?; Yose; Robert Turney; Corcoran Gallery of Art; S. Sadowsky; Charley Carroll; Spencer Smith; Caron Schwartz; Whalen, Philip; Uwe Montmann; Carmen Vigil; G.G. Lemaire; Oona; Francois Lagarde; Denise Mercedes; Peter Chowka; De Loach, Allen; David Mansfiled?; Mrs. DeLoach; Mr. and Mrs. J. Rothenberg; Oakton Community College; Nick Vaccaro; Joshua Hoffman; Orlovsky, Peter; Jonas; Leonard Cohen; Judy Daish; Joanna Voit; Joan Hammond?; John Sholee?; John Giorno; J. Rolhenberg?; Hollis Melton
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Images of Allen in Munich; Oakton Community College in Chicago, Illinois
      Chicago, Ill.; Munich, Germany; Oakton Community College; isolde ohlbaum
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1977 - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Images from Fried Shoes, Cooked Diamonds; V. N. disarmament demonstration in New York; Sacred Heart High School and Naropa University in Boulder, Colorado; Whole Earth Jamboree in San Francisco; Paterson, New Jersey; W.C.W. Day; Rocky Flats Protest; Writing Plutonian Ode; Rocky Flats Poetry Day in Colorado